[
    {
        "question": "ارثر",
        "answer": "ارثر"
    },
    {
        "question": "انجيلو",
        "answer": "انجيلو"
    },
    {
        "question":"آليا",
        "answer": "آليا"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبي",
        "answer": "روبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "answer": "ساسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "answer": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "الفا",
        "answer": "الفا"
    },
    {       
        "question": "شادو",
        "answer": "شادو"
    },
    {
        "question": "جين وو",
        "answer": "جين وو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اياتو",
        "answer": "اياتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساينو",
        "answer": "ساينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "شاو",
        "answer": "شاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوتاو",
        "answer": "هوتاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديهيا",
        "answer": "ديهيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "مونا",
        "answer": "مونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيوفيليت",
        "answer": "نيوفيليت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارليكينو",
        "answer": "ارليكينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيتلالي",
        "answer": "سيتلالي"
    },
    {
        "question": "الهيثم",
        "answer": "الهيثم"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناهيدا",
        "answer": "ناهيدا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فورينا",
        "answer": "فورينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "انجيلو عمك",
        "answer": "انجيلو عمك"
    },
    {
        "question": "اغريس",
        "answer": "اغريس"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "answer": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيودور",
        "answer": "فيودور"
    },
    {
        "question": "لومين",
        "answer": "لومين"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيل",
        "answer": "سيل"
    },
    {
        "question": "دازاي",
        "answer": "دازاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "توجي",
        "answer": "توجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساتورو",
        "answer": "ساتورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوجو",
        "answer": "غوجو"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيو وول",
        "answer": "بيو وول"
    },
    {
        "question": "سونغ",
        "answer": "سونغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "يويميا",
        "answer": "يويميا"
    },
    {
        "question": "مافويكا",
        "answer": "مافويكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليلي",
        "answer": "ليلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيدو",
        "answer": "سيدو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايثر",
        "answer": "ايثر"
    },
    {
        "question": "آي",
        "answer": "آي"
    }
]
